Everyone wants boring old bows and spears.
I like the more unusual stuff and about new can get unusual, like that spear our talk halls around an ice rail or that weapon of a raise.
What I wouldn't give to poke around inside one of those feel the lightning on my fingers.
So let's say someone you know happened to have a weapon like a raise.
You don't see for yourself.
Of course.
Look at that.
So the coils generate the spark, but the power source isn't even bolted in.
I won't lie.
She's beautiful, but there's beautiful.
And then there's beautiful.
What we need is a storm bird talent lining flows over them like water off a goose.
So we'd parts from a storm bird and a thunder draw, and you know where to find them.
That's right.
It's going to take some travelling, though.
A storm bird roost near the free heat.
I'll pack and meet you out there.
This will be fun.
Okay?
Hunted with me, I'll turn that weapon into your new best friend.
Second best
you
e can't do that
coming.
Yeah,
they're fits.
I just did a slot in one more
two.
It's some kind of
Maybe there's a clue nearby.
Did it
now to cheque the door
from Major Garrow to General Aaron Harris.
Subject Ultra.
We've progress, General.
You wanted fast, cheap and good.
And that's what we're going to deliver by using a flexible nano fibre weave instead of plating and enhancing protection with the 400 electron volts hard light micro projector.
We've reduced our testing cycle from weeks two days, and I'm confident we can get the suit out by next month with enough production to cover dozens of elite units at least.
Better yet, it will be half the weight half the cost and offered twice the mobility.
All we need is the balance of our funding, a few more texts and another experienced test subject.
I know resource is air stretched to the breaking point, but any more delays will jeopardise the schedule.
So please advise a set.
May God be with you and Jane in these dark times.
Semper fi major Garrow.
The clamps have the armour locked in place.
Thank you.
Maybe there's a way to power the mechanism.
Release the clamps.
I just need to instal these power cells.
That should do it.
Yeah,
getting soaked from melted snow.
Really?
You?
No,
I can't get out of this,
people.
Thank you.
Built all this
somebody memories.
It's not home anymore.
No roster.
I rust.
Uh, just take this off.
I don't want him listening in.
I lost it.
A lot has happened.
Killers from proving
they are gonna hurt anyone anymore.
We tracked them to devil's grief.
There was a battle
and we want tomorrow Here.
Made an impression.
Hasem mother issues.
But
I like him.
It was a bit so back.
She
couldn't have been my mother.
She was an old one.
She lived
ages ago.
Still, there is a Connexion.
The hatch.
It thought I was her.
It's
It's really strange.
Somehow
Elizabeth stopped war machines from destroying the world.
She couldn't save the civilisation of the old ones that was destroyed.
Obviously with life,
it's right.
She saved life
being devoured.
I need to know how Elizabeth stops the machines.
If I can find the weapons she built and use it,
the eclipse won't stand a chance.
Speaking of the eclipse,
I think I had a run in with Haiti's
picked up a focus and just like
cloud
dark swarner something
its voice.
It was terrible.
I don't know what Haiti's is or what it wants, but
it's evil.
No other way to describe I going to the grave.
Lord.
It lived up to its name.
Millions of people
fought and died to give us about the time she needed to finish.
Zero dawn.
The weapons she built.
It wasn't there.
I found out where she built it.
A secret base west of here.
Right?
Understand?
Fall
the capital of the Shadow Kharja.
So getting inside its
well, it's It's gonna take some doing before I can get into the zero Don base.
I'm gonna have to crash the Eclipse Focus network.
It's Yeah, it's complicated.
I know where to go.
Silence says it won't be too dangerous.
But since when do I trust him?
I've got to do it.
I need to know what it was built.
The weapon that stopped the war machines and the Connexion between us, It's
It's still a mystery
when I intend to solve.
Yes, I I should be going
What?
You
come on.
Going down fast.
You know, I kind of missed all this red dust.
Well, there's our storm bird.
When you're ready I'll follow up and boom
store Invert strong against Shaq Blaze Canister engine destroying This component disables the dive.
Maley Attack!
Freeze!
Canister!
Lightning gun!
Destroying this component disables the range.
Shock attacks.
I'm going.
Yeah,
yeah,
Just that She could include storms.
Just stay out of their way from now.
Yeah,
Thank you.
Go
found the part one Storm Bird Town.
Let's do it.
I haven't had this much fun in ages.
Watch and learn.
A Loy only don't stare directly at the sparks.
Okay, so I pretty much had to break her in half.
But what's a staff?
A stick.
One thing I like about sticks.
You can put them back together.
However you want, which you did.
This thing looks a whole lot more dangerous.
She's better than dangerous.
She's a genuine var.
Just special.
Now take good care of her.
Never thought I'd be glad to see the inside of a thunder Jaws Mouth, I sure am Every machines a big box of tools.
Once you stop trying to kill you, that isthe Trust me A loy You won't recognise this ice rail when I'm through
there.
Ah, she's perfect.
Ah Spears A spear!
Right Poke slash Done.
Boring.
I adjusted the chilled water flow re balanced here, strapped on a launcher and now she shoots freezing spikes.
Tutta.
You weren't kidding.
More beautiful, more powerful.
That was some impressive work.
Georgia.
Hey, it's nothing.
I just helped her become what she was always meant to be.
They grow up so fast.
Show me what you had in mind for the 40 Fire finally was feeling like I neglected her.
And that's a little too close to my family life.
She's done and she's yours.
Don't do anything I wouldn't do.
House looks great.
I almost expected you to turn it into a burning rope.
Castor or something?
Nah, she was close to perfect from the start.
She's a barge original after all.
You've done good work with this weapon.
Varga told you I was good.
Anyway, I'm glad she's in your hands.
Thanks for Gia.
These three weapons, they're fine work.
Are you kidding?
I can't remember when I had this much fun.
I should be thanking you.
I'm the one walking away with the weapons.
Aren't seems wrong to charge you for giving me an opportunity to do what I love doing.
Don't tell pop.
I said that
here.
Whenever tinker with weapons, I go through fistfuls of this stuff.
Maybe you'll get some use out of it.
What?
Okay,
Being you.
Thank you.